{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Flat Roof Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564376523369pwspr015F22724D8FA4DFF8FD65C05DD318E5A42.pwspr009-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40394/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40394,"taskName":"Flat, Foam, or Single Ply Roofing - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace a Flat, Foam or Single Ply Roof","xmTaskDescriptor":"Flat Roof Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":4912,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Flat Roofing roofs exterior build","textMessagingName":"Inst Flat Roof","rolloverLongDesc":"Several technologies are used to create waterproof flat roofs, though most firms are skilled in several methods. This category is for when it is probable that repairs won't be sufficient \u0026 that total replacement is likely to be necessary.","rolloverShortDesc":"Built-up roofs, tar \u0026 gravel, bitumen, foam, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace a Flat, Foam or Single Ply Roof.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Flat Roof Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Foam \u0026 Single Ply Roofing","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":65,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Flat Foam / Single Ply Roof Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Flat, Foam, or Single Ply Roofing - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Flat Roof Project","urlName":"Flat-Foam-or-Single-Ply-Roofing-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Flat Roof Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Cost Info, Reviews","searchKeywords":"Flat,Roofing,roofs,exterior,build,Systems,Rubber,License,exchange,Roofers,roof,designs,bids,,prosource,prescreened,national,local,rooofing,siding,,conctractors,roofers.com,wanted,replacement,Ply,Foam,Single","emcCategoryOid":-12061,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":688,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40394/":{"taskOID":40394,"originalTaskOID":40394,"setID":688,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6869,"questionDisplayText":"What is the nature of this project?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":9813,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Completely replace roof","answerDisplayText":"Completely replace roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9814,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install roof on new construction","answerDisplayText":"Install roof on new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9815,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing roof","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5257,"questionDisplayText":"Roofing Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of roofing material would you prefer?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1172,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Built Up/Tar \u0026 Gravel","answerDisplayText":"Built Up/Tar \u0026 Gravel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5717,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Single Ply Rubberized","answerDisplayText":"Single Ply Rubberized","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5975,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sprayed Polyurethane Foam","answerDisplayText":"Sprayed Polyurethane Foam","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5381,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Rolled/Torch Down","answerDisplayText":"Rolled/Torch Down","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6872,"questionDisplayText":"Stories in House","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6871,"questionDisplayText":"Are you aware of any leaks or damage to the roof?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you aware of any leaks or damage to the roof?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5568,"questionDisplayText":"Special Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which special features would you like for your roof?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5354,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ridge vent","answerDisplayText":"Ridge vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5842,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Snow guards or brackets","answerDisplayText":"Snow guards or brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2893,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters and downspouts","answerDisplayText":"Gutters and downspouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Turbine vents","answerDisplayText":"Turbine vents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5769,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Skylight/Solar tube","answerDisplayText":"Skylight/Solar tube","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2950,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat tape","answerDisplayText":"Heat tape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6857,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Water diverters","answerDisplayText":"Water diverters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2521,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6869,"questionDisplayText":"What is the nature of this project?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":9813,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Completely replace roof","answerDisplayText":"Completely replace roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9814,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install roof on new construction","answerDisplayText":"Install roof on new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9815,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing roof","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9813,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Completely replace roof","answerDisplayText":"Completely replace roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9814,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install roof on new construction","answerDisplayText":"Install roof on new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9815,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing roof","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5257,"questionDisplayText":"Roofing Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of roofing material would you prefer?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1172,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Built Up/Tar \u0026 Gravel","answerDisplayText":"Built Up/Tar \u0026 Gravel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5717,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Single Ply Rubberized","answerDisplayText":"Single Ply Rubberized","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5975,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sprayed Polyurethane Foam","answerDisplayText":"Sprayed Polyurethane Foam","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5381,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Rolled/Torch Down","answerDisplayText":"Rolled/Torch Down","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1172,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Built Up/Tar \u0026 Gravel","answerDisplayText":"Built Up/Tar \u0026 Gravel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5717,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Single Ply Rubberized","answerDisplayText":"Single Ply Rubberized","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5975,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sprayed Polyurethane Foam","answerDisplayText":"Sprayed Polyurethane Foam","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5381,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Rolled/Torch Down","answerDisplayText":"Rolled/Torch Down","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6872,"questionDisplayText":"Stories in House","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6871,"questionDisplayText":"Are you aware of any leaks or damage to the roof?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you aware of any leaks or damage to the roof?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5568,"questionDisplayText":"Special Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which special features would you like for your roof?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5354,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ridge vent","answerDisplayText":"Ridge vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5842,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Snow guards or brackets","answerDisplayText":"Snow guards or brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2893,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters and downspouts","answerDisplayText":"Gutters and downspouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Turbine vents","answerDisplayText":"Turbine vents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5769,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Skylight/Solar tube","answerDisplayText":"Skylight/Solar tube","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2950,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat tape","answerDisplayText":"Heat tape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6857,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Water diverters","answerDisplayText":"Water diverters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2521,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5354,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ridge vent","answerDisplayText":"Ridge vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5842,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Snow guards or brackets","answerDisplayText":"Snow guards or brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2893,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters and downspouts","answerDisplayText":"Gutters and downspouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Turbine vents","answerDisplayText":"Turbine vents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5769,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Skylight/Solar tube","answerDisplayText":"Skylight/Solar tube","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2950,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat tape","answerDisplayText":"Heat tape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6857,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Water diverters","answerDisplayText":"Water diverters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2521,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}